[seagulls squawking]
[muffled club music playing]
[club music intensifies]
[club music continues]
[indistinct chatter]
[playful whistling]
[whistling]
[woman laughing]
[inaudible]
[both laughing]
Okay. Tatiana, what is going on?
What do you mean,
what is going on?
Well, TJ is obsessed with you
and you're just
ignoring the poor guy.
Are you guys fighting?
[chuckling] We're good, Kayle.
We're good.
No! Why don't I believe you?
You are literally the nosiest
person I've ever met.
You love it. Now talk.
Okay, look.
In September, he transfers
to work for his dad's CPA.
I start my degree.
I mean, Boston is a long way
from San Francisco.
Are you guys breaking up?
We're taking a break.
Now, Kayle,
can we have fun, please?
Why did you not
tell me about this?
[Kayle continues indistinctly,
squeals]
Hey, one minute, one minute.
Here.
-Jesus.
-Oh, incoming.
-What?
-[in Spanish]
Um...
No?
[in English] Not today, guys.
-Ah! Sorry.
-It's okay.
[man in Spanish]
-We bring drinks.
-[grunts] Hi, baby.
-Hi.
-[both moaning]
-How are you doing?
-Doing good.
-All good?
-Yeah.
What took you so long?
-What took us so long?
-[Kayle] Yeah!
Your boy was trying
to show off his español skills
with the bartender.
That's what took so long.
-But you don't speak Spanish.
-But Google Translate does.
[Kayle] How'd that go?
Oh, my God! You did not. Stop.
And that's why
we now have tequila shots.
-Shots, baby!
-Yeah!
[cheering]
[chuckles]
[Tatiana] Mm. Mmm.
-[glass clinks]
-That's smooth.
You're smooth.
-[TJ] Nice.
-Yeah.
-[groans]
-Wait. Where's Kyle?
Oh, he's gone.
Danny. What the fuck?
-I'm not his babysitter.
-He's not gone.
-He's around here somewhere.
-Babe.
Where is he, TJ?
Look, I said he's fine.
This isn't his vibe.
He's doing his own thing.
[sinister music playing]
[waitress in Spanish]
[in English] No. I'm good.
[in Spanish]
My friend.
Drinks are free
when you're playing at my table.
Just like Vegas.
-[Kyle] I'm good.
-Okay.
[inhales then exhales deeply]
[player 1] The way you stare
at those cards
makes me excited to see how
this is gonna turn out, Kyle?
I don't think you're gonna
like this one too much.
All in.
Hold on. I got 450 more.
My sister's gonna kill me
for that.
[player 1 in Spanish]
[in English]
We got a ballsy one right here.
Oh, that you do.
You know what?
[sighs then chuckles]
I'm gonna call it because
I think you are full of shit.
Full house.
Oh, well, you weren't
full of shit after all.
[Kyle] No, sir.
And you got a pretty good part
in there, you know?
Yeah. [sighs]
So, what do you think
you'll spend all that money on?
[Kyle] Pay back my sister.
She invited me out here
with some friends.
I got myself into some trouble
the last couple of years,
and, well, she's always been
there for me.
This would be a great way
to take care of her for once.
[player 1] Isn't that sweet
and wonderful?
It brings tears to my eyes.
It almost breaks my heart...
to do this to you.
[ominous music playing]
Four of a kind.
I thought I had it.
[player 1 chuckles] Victory
and loss walk hand in hand.
I'm sorry, kid.
But you know what?
Your story really got me.
So, I'm gonna do something
really nice for you
and your sister.
-Thanks. I don't know...
-[stammers] On the back.
Shark diving?
-Have you ever been?
-No.
What? You and your friends
will love it.
The capitán of the boat
is a very good friend of mine.
Just call that number,
and I'll set you up
for tomorrow afternoon.
Are you free?
Yeah, sure.
I'll make sure
he takes care of you.
Thank you.
Burns. Esteban Burns.
[Kyle] Thank you, Burns.
[player 2 in Spanish]
[club music playing in distance]
It'll change your life,
I promise you.
[club music continues]
-[stammers] Sorry.
-[man sucks teeth]
[retches then breathing shakily]
Who you texting?
Holy shit. You asshole!
-Where the hell have you been?
-[TJ] He's back!
-What's up?
-How are you, brother?
-Great.
-[Kayle] Kyle!
-Hey! How are you doing, man?
-What up, kid?
-So...
-What's up?
-Did you win?
-Fuck, yeah, I did.
Hey, hey! Win what?
Kyle, were you gambling?
Of course not. Jesus.
Don't spoil the vibe, T.
All right? Doing shots?
-Hey, hey! Water for you.
-Shots.
Water.
-Water shots.
-[Danny] Shots.
Hey, you know what, guys?
To show my appreciation
for you all inviting me
along on your trip,
I've got something set up for us
you're gonna absolutely love.
Sunset cruise on a catamaran,
please.
Even better, all right?
Just wait for me tomorrow
at 8 at the reception.
It's gonna be awesome.
-You're in?
-I'm in.
-It's gonna be awesome.
-[Kayle] We're in.
-Okay? Yeah?
-Thank you.
All right. YOLO, baby.
-YO, YO, YO, YOLO.
-YOLO!
-Whoo!
-Yeah. Was I this bad?
You were way worse.
-Worse than that?
-Oh, yeah.
-Wait.
-[Kyle] Jesus.
-Sorry about that.
-It's okay.
Thanks for always being there
for me.
Of course. Of course.
Now, drink your water.
-Come on.
-[Danny] Don't worry, baby.
I'll get you a little
apple juice next time.
I'd like to see you try
being a year sober.
-[TJ] Hey.
-You'd do it?
[Danny] Absolutely not.
It's good tequila.
[woman] I'm sorry.
What was the name again?
The name is Kyle Scott. He has
an excursion booked for us.
Hey, let me hit her
with the Google Translate.
[in Spanish]
[in English]
Hey, what are you doing?
Signing in.
Sorry. There's been
a misunderstanding.
Okay. No problem.
Hotel excursion? Are you crazy?
I set up my own thing.
Trust me, my guy is just
as good as the hotel's guy.
If not better. All right?
And you know what?
We don't have to be on a boat
with a bunch of other tourists.
-A private boat?
-Yes!
-It is a sunset cruise. It is.
-Hmm...
Nope, shark cage diving.
-[ominous music playing]
-Wait, what? Sharks?
Yeah. Shark diving.
Like in a cage.
-Oh, no.
-Shit. How'd you swing that?
This could be amazing, actually.
-This could be awesome.
-See, your man is down.
What do you think, T?
It could be fun.
Come on.
We're in a cage?
Yeah, it's totally legit.
Fine.
I will have reception go call us
a cab. What is the address?
The address is right here
on the back.
"Captain Logan's
Shark Experience."
-Looks legit.
-[Tatiana] Okay, wait.
Kyle, you were gambling?
-No.
-[Danny] Hold on.
This is where you got the boat?
Yes.
This is gonna be
some Tinder shit.
There is no way this boat
looks like that.
We'll see, man.
-[Tatiana] Kyle.
-Twenty bucks.
-Danny!
-Let's do it.
You go in the cage,
cage goes in the water,
-you go in the water.
-All right.
-Sharks.
-All right. Too close.
-I get it.
-[singsongy] Farewell
and adieu to you,
fair Spanish ladies.
-Farewell and adieu.
-[chuckling]
[Kayle] Giddy up, cowboy.
[chuckles]
[Danny continues singing
indistinctly]
[Niko Rubio's "Besito" playing]
[TJ] Um... That...
That should do it.
-[taxi driver] Okay.
-Is that okay?
-[camera shutter clicks]
-[in Spanish]
Hey, you wanna hold up?
I... I feel like
a bit of a minion there.
Sorry. I'm just thinking about
my brother.
I know. Just looks a bit weird
for the rest of the group
is all.
I know, just,
why did he lie to me?
[stammers] I thought we were
gonna keep it the way it was.
You know, at least
until after the vacation.
I'm just starting to feel
a little dishonest to you.
All I'm asking is that we walk
together. Is that okay?
Hey.
Did you know?
[bird squawking]
Look, T, we talked about this.
All right? Kyle...
He's a grown adult.
-Forget about your brother.
-[Kyle speaks indistinctly]
We need to focus on us.
-T, we're gonna work this out.
-Not now.
[salsa music playing
over speakers]
Hi! We gotta get a picture,
everybody. Come on.
Who knows
when we'll be together again.
-Come on, baby.
-Come on. Come on.
Smile, everyone. Look cute.
-[camera shutter clicks]
-Very cute.
Mexico, baby!
-[Kyle sighs]
-That's the boat?
Told ya. Come on, pay up.
You Burns's group?
That's us.
Permission to come aboard?
Welcome aboard.
[salsa music continues]
What are your names?
Kyle.
-Tatiana.
-Welcome.
-[in Spanish] Hi, Captain!
-[in English] Welcome.
Mr. Burns
is taking care of everything.
So there's beer and snacks, huh?
Make yourselves at home.
[groaning] There we go.
So, Kyle, you're the man
that played his hand
like he was trying to lose it,
I hear.
Yeah? Well, we'll be setting off
in a few moments, guys.
Just waiting for a few more.
There they are.
Uh... Excuse me, Logan.
Sorry, Captain.
I think there's been
a misunderstanding.
Burns said it was gonna be
a private boat
for just my friends and me.
That's right.
So who else is coming?
Oh, no one
you need to worry about.
Mr. Burns
said to take care of you.
That's what I'm going to do.
[eerie music playing]
Are we still waiting
for another fella in your party?
We're the party, Captain.
Let's go.
You go join your friends, Kyle.
We're going to have
a nice time, all right?
Yeah. Sounds good.
[salsa music continues]
[Tatiana]
Just let me talk to him.
-Hey.
-[Kyle] What's up?
-Who the hell are those guys?
-No idea.
Yeah, I thought you said
this was a private cruise, man.
Don't worry about it, okay?
The captain said we're good.
-Hey, come here.
-What?
The captain said our drinks
were comped? I mean...
-Who's paying for this?
-You worry too much.
You promised me, Kyle.
Look, I found a low-stakes game.
-[sighs]
-The guy I played with
is kind of a big deal.
And for some reason,
he liked me.
And he hooked me up
with this Logan dude.
I know I shouldn't
have played cards.
Look at this.
I wanna trust you, Kyle.
It was a one-off, T.
Scout's honor.
All right,
let's have some fun, baby.
Viva la vacay!
Viva la vacay, bitches!
Come on.
[techno music playing]
[engine revving]
[boat horn blares]
[techno music continues]
[music stops]
[Logan] All right.
I'm assuming
you've all been diving before?
[TJ] Yes, sir.
Sure, but not
for a while, though.
If I say no,
is that going to be a problem?
Aren't you supposed
to take a PADI test?
Just say yes.
-Yes.
-Okay.
Let's do a quick refresh,
shall we?
You have your face mask.
It acts as a regulator
so you can breathe.
You'll be able to talk
to each other down there.
But if you want to talk to me,
just move this blue toggle,
all right?
Otherwise, I can't hear you.
There's your pressure gauge.
Tells you how much air you have.
Your dive computer tells you
how low you are.
-Are the sharks dangerous?
-[Logan] Ah! The sharks!
Let me tell you
about the sharks.
Generally,
a shark is a cautious animal
with a curious disposition.
They're not blood-thirsty
monsters,
but they are Apex predators.
So keep your head in a swivel
and stay calm.
Anyways, your dive vest is
equipped with a tourniquet
in case you start bleeding
to death.
You won't need it,
but it's there.
-What's this for?
-No, don't mess with that.
-That's your BCD.
-My what?
It's your
Buoyancy Control Device.
If you inflate it, you'll just
float to the top of the cage.
All right. Any questions? No?
Let's do this.
[muffled]
I don't think I can breathe.
-[all laughing]
-[Logan] Oh.
Make sure you turn on your air.
-That's my man. [laughs]
-[Logan] And breathe evenly.
If you get excited
or you start hyperventilating,
that's when things go wrong,
all right?
Off you go.
Bye, fellas.
[Kayle, singsongy]
Going down, down, down, down.
Hey, Captain.
How deep are you dropping them?
Oh, just a few meters.
You don't have to go too deep
to see anything around here.
[ominous music playing]
[man 1 sighs]
You got something on your face.
[inhales deeply then exhales]
[softly] That was
a fucking mess, man.
Yes, it was. [sighs]
Yeah. Fucked up.
Don't tell your mom,
because she's gonna tell mine.
[Kayle and Tatiana chattering]
I dropped the Sig, man.
Lost it.
Who cares? What's done is done.
[man 2] Well, I got my backup.
[Tatiana] Oh my God. So cute!
[chattering continues]
Check out the debutants, G.
Spoiled rich kids.
Martin. Martin!
We don't need any more trouble.
Whatever, man.
I'm gonna have a smoke.
Burns told us to stay put
until he gets here.
Fuck, Burns. I need a smoke.
Leave those behind.
Tell you what, when this
ball-twister of a job is over,
I may trust you again.
Until then, I watch my bags
and you watch yours, yeah?
[sighs] Suit yourself.
Yeah.
-[laughing]
-Okay, okay. Enough.
[Kayle] Are you gonna tell me
why we're mad at TJ?
And what the hell is going on
with Kyle?
[Tatiana] Stop.
We're not mad at TJ,
and I don't know
what is going on with Kyle.
-Okay. Hold on. Yes! Work it.
-[camera shutter clicks]
Hello?
[exhales]
Can we help you?
You wanna take this creepy vibe
somewhere else on the boat?
Anywhere else, really.
Not around my passengers, bud.
[exhales] Come on, Captain.
Who says?
[Logan chuckles]
The smoking area
is in the front deck.
Best view in the house,
all right?
I'm fine.
The view is fine right here.
Don't you think?
It's okay, ladies. [chuckles]
[G] Martin.
Bye, Martin.
Keep a leash on your boyfriend,
Garrison.
How's it going down there,
fellas?
[Kyle] Oh, yeah. We're having
the time of our lives.
There's absolutely nothing
down here.
[Logan] Well, I think we can do
something about that.
Ladies.
Would you all like
to help me feed the sharks?
Grab a piece of fish and start
throwing it in the water.
[Tatiana mutters]
[splashing]
Are we chumming now?
Well, sharks have a sensitive
olfactory system
that allows them to detect blood
at concentrations as low
as one part per million.
That's a quarter of a mile
to you and me.
This stuff is nasty.
-[Logan laughs]
-[Tatiana chuckles] Oh my God!
Shark's an opportunist.
You know, he eats once a week.
If he doesn't have to hunt,
he won't.
So throw some more chum
in the water.
[Kayle]
Hey, T, what are you doing?
Oh, you know, just chumming
as you do.
-[Logan laughs]
-[splashing]
-A good job, by the way.
-[Tatiana giggles]
Kayle, stop it. You're gonna
get over here right now.
-No! I don't need to do it.
-Come on! Come on!
Ew. God, what does it feel like?
No, not for me.
-It's okay.
-Come on, do it.
-Do it, do it, do it, do it!
-Okay, okay. [squeals]
-You did it!
-I did it!
Good job, good job.
[Martin chuckles] God,
that smells like shit, right?
I mean, rank-a-fucking shit.
I can smell it all the way
at the end of the boat.
[giggles]
No wonder the sharks
are pissed off, right, Cap?
-[Logan] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-[laughs] Well, check it out.
-[heavy bubbling]
-God, I hate the fucking sea.
[Tatiana] Is that a shark?
-[Logan] Coming around, guys.
-Oh my God. Right there!
-Ooh, yeah. That's it.
-[Martin laughs]
-There's another one.
-[squeals]
-Holy shit! Holy shit!
-Okay, do it. Oh my God.
[Kayle squeals]
-You got it! Do it! Come on.
-[Kayle] Ugh!
Jesus Christ!
Do you see them?
No. Nothing yet.
It's pretty quiet.
[air hissing]
Oh! Check it out.
What is that?
Is that a great white?
[Logan] No, kids.
Those are Mako sharks.
[Danny] I've seen those online.
They eat people.
[Logan] They'll be in a shiver.
Keep an eye out.
They'll come at you
from the shadows.
-[Danny] Shiver me timbers.
-It's your birthday.
[Logan] A group of sharks
is called a shiver.
Hey, Kyle. Take our picture.
What kind of shark
did he say that was?
[Kyle] Mako, but you tell
everyone it's a great white.
Smile. No one will know
the difference.
[Danny] Right.
-Man, what are you doing?
-I'm taking a video.
-You gonna drop your phone.
-I have the strap on.
Hold on. Let me try something.
Here, sharky, sharky.
[Kyle] And that's how TJ
lost his hand.
[Danny] Dude!
That was a great shot.
-Get it to come back.
-Now you're just being stupid.
[TJ] Oh, shit.
-[Danny and TJ snickering]
-Shit!
[TJ] Watch out!
[snickering]
-[Danny] Dude, you asshole!
-Come on. That was hilarious.
[Danny] I dropped my phone,
you dick bag.
-[TJ] That was pretty funny.
-[Danny] To who? The shark?
That was a new phone.
You know what? I'll get it.
[Danny]
We're in shark-infested waters.
-Are you kidding?
-I'm bigger than that thing.
-It's not gonna mess with me.
-I don't know, man.
They prefer seafood, remember?
I've been diving before.
[high-pitched ringing]
[TJ] I'll be right back.
Don't worry.
[Danny] We are not telling
the girls about this.
[Kyle]
Yeah, definitely a bad idea.
[Logan] How's it going down
there, fellas?
[Danny] We're doing fine.
[Kyle] Yeah, everything's good.
-They sound scared.
-They do.
We gotta...
Hey, can we talk to them?
Yeah. Press that button.
The red button there.
Hey, boys. How is it?
[Kyle] Cool, you know?
Fish and ocean.
Oh! Check out all the sea life.
Did you just say
-you wanted more chum?
-Hmm!
No, no, no. We're good.
Kayle, no. No, no! No more chum.
-Big yes.
-Ha!
[both muttering, squealing]
-Oh my... Oh my God.
-[splashing]
-I'm gonna fucking kill you!
-I'm so sorry.
Great, more chum.
-[squealing]
-[splashing]
[Martin] Fuck.
Jesus Christ! Look at that.
[Logan] Oh, yeah. [chuckles]
[Kayle squeals] Oh my God.
They're coming down, boys!
Damn it!
Kyle, you see TJ anywhere?
No. And I don't see the shark.
Maybe they are just full
from other fish we fed them.
Damn it. Why does TJ
always have to be the hero?
[suspenseful music playing]
-[both yell]
-[snickering]
[air hissing]
[Danny] Damn it, TJ.
[Kyle, sarcastically]
Ha-ha. That was good.
That was a good one.
-[TJ] Look what I got.
-Attaboy.
It was recording the whole time.
It was easy to find.
[TJ yells] Oh my God!
-TJ! Watch out!
-Holy shit!
-[music intensifies]
-Goddamn it!
[TJ] Did you guys see that?
Are you okay?
-Yeah.
-[Danny] That was crazy, man.
I didn't realize
they were so big.
That thing came out of nowhere.
[device beeping]
I'll bring you up.
[Danny] We were just starting
to have fun.
[Kyle] Again, we are not
telling the ladies about this.
-Absolutely.
-No shit.
Did you see the size
of that thing?
-Are you sure you're okay?
-Yeah.
-[Tatiana] Is that hot?
-Show me. Yeah.
Listen.
Look at our sexy little guppies.
-[chucking]
-Hey. How was it, guys?
It was an experience, for sure.
[chuckling]
Danny, baby, how was it?
Well, there's,
like, fish and water and shit.
-Kyle, how was it?
-Yeah, it was... great.
[Velcro ripping]
[Tatiana] Okay.
All right, ladies,
let's get your gear on.
You're up next.
-[Tatiana] Okay, Kayle.
-Follow me.
Let's do this.
Boys, watch how it's done.
-Miss me.
-I will.
-I'll be fine.
-Bye, baby.
Man, that was sketchy.
Oh, fuck.
-[TJ] You're gonna love it.
-Yeah?
Yeah, it really is amazing.
You want me
to come down with you or...?
No. You stay here
with your little boyfriends.
[mockingly] Oh, burn!
-Stay in the cage.
-Yes, baby. There's a reason
women tend to live longer
than men. Don't worry.
Okay. Into the cage, ladies.
Oh, one more thing.
If you get into any trouble,
there's a speargun
in the case in the cage.
Anything gets too close,
give it a poke, okay?
How come we never heard
about the speargun?
Alcohol and spearguns don't mix.
[Tatiana] Hmm.
[Kayle] Wow.
Oh my God, T,
I can't believe
we're doing this.
[Tatiana] It's so incredible.
It's so crazy.
I mean, it's just
so beautiful down here.
Look. You could totally tell
who the alphas are
and who's just following
the alphas around.
-Hmm. Like you and TJ?
-Oh, shut up. [giggles]
How's it going down there,
ladies?
[Tatiana] We're in complete awe.
-Do you see the sharks?
-No.
I hope they've gone.
I think your hinky tendencies
scared them away.
-What does that even mean?
-I don't know.
Well, hopefully,
they'll come back.
[Logan snickers]
[sniffles]
Yeah.
You know what, guys?
You know what I think?
Maybe you should throw
some more of those fish guts
down there, yeah?
Scare the girls. [snickers]
Nah, I think we're good.
Okay, I gotta take your photo.
-You look really hot right now.
-Yeah, really?
Seriously. Hold on, hold on.
I am obsessed with
this whole look. Obsessed.
I'm gonna grab another drink.
Do you want one?
I'm good.
Can you grab me a dry shirt?
Yeah. Of course.
[Danny] Yo, TJ.
What the fuck is in your bag?
[ominous music playing]
-Oh, shit.
-[Garrison] Hey!
Put this back, please.
[Martin] Yo, man. Yo, yo.
What are you doing, buddy?
That's my bag.
What are you doing
going through my bag?
[Danny] I thought
it was TJ's bag, man.
I didn't want
to go through your shit.
Well, it wasn't TJ's bag.
It was my bag.
[stammers] Whoa, whoa.
The fuck you're doing with that?
What is that?
What does it look like?
I'm a nobody, man.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
A nobody
with a very expensive...
That's a $15,000 Rolex
you're wearing, pal.
Daddy give it to you?
Ah. Yeah. I worked my ass off
my whole life, man.
I don't have a Rolex like that,
right?
Doesn't seem fair to me.
You're not a nobody, 'cause
somebody cares for you, man.
And that somebody
would pay a lot more
than the value of that Rolex...
for you.
Put the gun away, Martin.
Hey, man. You want the watch?
Take the watch, man.
Right?
I mean, it's Martin, right?
Just take it, please.
I really don't give a shit
what you guys are into.
I didn't hear or see anything.
I'm not gonna tell anybody.
Just fucking let me--
It's okay, man.
I don't want your watch.
I don't need your watch.
Keep it.
But you shouldn't have
called me "Martin."
-[grunting]
-Danny!
Shut up! Stay down, both of you.
Stay right there.
Goddamn it!
Well, that was a bad decision.
[Tatiana] Cute, I love it.
[chuckles]
-What...? What is that?
-What?
-It looks like Danny.
-Danny?
-[Tatiana] Danny! Hey, Danny!
-Hey!
Hey, hey.
Hey. Hey, Kayle.
We cannot go out there.
[Kayle] What the hell
is happening? Is this a prank?
-Calm down. Shit!
-Danny! Oh my God.
[Tatiana] TJ! Kyle!
-Why is Danny down here?
-What is going on?
What are they doing?
Burns told me that you two
are supposed to be incognito.
Well, we were, Cap,
until he opened the fucking bag.
Get on your knees, man!
Right here.
There you go, pretty boy.
G-man, you're with me, right?
[Tatiana and Kayle
yelling over radio]
[Garrison] Hey.
-Do as he says.
-Get on your knees.
-[Kayle over radio] Hello?
-Hands behind your heads.
Garrison, tell your boy
that this vessel
belongs to Esteban Burns.
He doesn't want
this kind of heat
to jeopardize
this whole operation.
-You know that.
-He knows.
-[exhales] Okay.
-You are some kind of stupid,
you know that?
[Martin]
Turn that radio off, Captain.
Now, before I lose
my goddamn mind.
[Tatiana]
Hello? Is anybody there?
[Kayle] What is going on?
I need to check on him.
-I need to get out of this.
-Do not open this cage.
-We have to stay here, okay?
-How do I open this cage?
-Hey.
-Where's the door?
-[thud]
-[both yelling, panting]
-What was that?
-[Tatiana mutters]
Oh my gosh. Oh my God.
Kayle, is that...?
Is that a fucking great white?
-[both gasp, yell]
-[Tatiana] Okay.
Stay in the center of the cage.
Stay in the center.
-Hold on.
-What the hell is happening?
-I think it's gone. Okay.
-Why aren't they answering?
[pants] Will somebody
answer us, please?
-[engine humming in distance]
-Just breathe. Wait, listen.
Do you hear that?
[Kayle] What is that?
[ominous music playing]
[engine stops]
[inhales then exhales]
[exhales then chuckles]
[in Spanish]
El Gaitero.
[chuckles]
[in English] Kyle?
Mr. Burns.
[stutters] Why is Kyle,
my friend, on his knees?
Your lads made a balls of it.
A proper balls.
Garrison?
I stayed with the product
like you said, boss. Ask him.
Martin?
Okay, look, one of them
got nosey and went into the bag,
so I fixed him.
Where is he now?
-Down there.
-[Garrison] Martin shot him.
Martin. Martin. Martin.
Just remind me.
What is my number one rule?
Never leave the bag
out of your sight.
Yeah. So what happened?
-I don't know. I mean...
-Oh, come on...
You know.
It's a little boat, boss,
I went for a cigarette there,
and I just... I must've...
Let your bag out of your sight.
-Yeah.
-[grunts]
So now listen to me,
you little prick.
I don't make rules
for my health.
I make them
so things move clean,
money flows, no noise, no blood.
But when you break the rules,
people do get hurt.
So now I want you to apologize
to Kyle and his friends
because you ruined the beautiful
plan I have for them
because you couldn't follow
the rules!
-Boss?
-You heard me.
Then after you apologize,
I want you...
to, uh...
kill them.
-What?
-No, come on.
Let's just talk this through,
okay?
Please, Esteban.
This is my boat.
No. Right now, this is my boat.
And on my boat, no loose ends.
Oh, please,
you don't have to do this.
Mr. Burns, please,
please, don't do this.
-[TJ] Kyle!
-[Garrison] Stay there!
[stammering]
What are you doing, Martin?
-What?
-I said, "Apologize first."
-[Martin] Really, boss?
-Yes, really, Martin. Really.
Now, say it with me.
"I am sorry I messed up
your outing." Say it.
"I'm sorry I messed up
your outing."
-"I didn't follow the rules."
-You don't sound sincere.
-"I don't sound sincere."
-No, don't say that.
-[grunts]
[groaning, grunting]
-[in Spanish]
-[yells]
-Hey.
-I don't give a shit about you
or your drugs or your business
or any of it, okay?
-[Burns] Yeah. Okay.
-Just let us walk.
We never saw anything.
You'll never see us again.
[Martin groans]
Jesus Christ.
[exhales] Wow.
[in Spanish]
[Delgado] That's right.
[mutters in English]
-[chokes]
-[Burns exhales]
-[TJ groans]
-[scoffs then clicks tongue]
You know? [stammers]
This wasn't
how it was supposed to be.
In my world,
you would have done your thing,
I would have done mine.
I'm sorry, but I can't
let you or your friends
get in the way of my business.
-It's nothing personal.
-[coughs]
-I hope you understand.
-[TJ gasps for air]
[Burns] Ay...
[groans]
Uh... [stammers]
[coughs then groans]
Take care of the bodies.
[groaning]
Hey, hey, hey! No!
[groans]
[sighs then sniffles]
[Martin] He's-- [groans]
[sighs]
Fuck...
What are they doing?
Something's going on up there.
-Oh my God, TJ!
-Oh my God!
-Oh my God, TJ! TJ!
-TJ! TJ! Can you hear us?
-Just...
-Why isn't he moving?
-Oh my God.
-TJ!
-[Kayle] What is going on?
This can't be happening.
This can't be happening!
[sobbing] Oh my God.
Martin.
-Martin.
-Okay, boss, man.
I get it, okay? I...
-I made a mistake, okay?
-No. This is not a mistake.
This is a failure.
And failures have consequences.
Consequences?
Now, go get the bag.
-I'm covered in blood.
-I know. Go get my bag.
I don't think
you understand, boss.
There's no way I'm going
in there covered in blood.
-There's sharks down there...
-One job.
That's all you had.
Garrison,
I paid for three couriers.
Where is the third man?
The meet was complicated.
Four men died. One was ours.
But you got your product.
But who is gonna get my bag?
[Martin] What about the girls
in the cage, boss?
There is more?
There's two down there.
I thought you knew that.
But this is so perfect.
[stammers]
How do I talk to her?
Push the button.
It'll turn the comm back on.
[clears throat] Hello?
[Tatiana mutters] Captain Logan?
No.
Who is this?
Uh... I asked you first.
[Tatiana] Hey!
We don't have time for this.
What the fuck
is going on up there?
Two of our friends are dead.
[Burns] Well, actually three.
-What?
-Listen, things were...
-[sobbing] No, no, no.
-They went really crazy
-up here.
-Kyle...
I'm going to need you to listen
to what I have to say.
-Do you understand?
-[sobbing over radio]
The man who went overboard...
Uh... Had a bag.
Now, in the bag,
there are some very important
items that belong to me.
[softly] What's her name?
-[Logan] Tatiana.
-Tatiana. So, Tatiana.
By the way, that's
a beautiful name, Tatiana.
Yeah. So give me my bag.
You know, enough people
have been hurt for this,
so bring it back.
You walk free, I disappear,
and we have a deal.
What do you think?
-[panting] I can't breathe.
-Okay. Breathe, breathe.
You have to tell him "yes."
Okay, T?
What do you say?
Listen, T, tell him "yes."
We don't have a choice, do we?
I know, I know. Okay?
[Tatiana] Deal.
Very good. Bye.
This is crazy.
I'll go get the bag.
-Leave her out of this.
-No, you don't. No.
You and your boat are too
important to my operations.
No, no, no. She'll do fine.
[snickers] Unless the sharks
get them first, right?
Well, if the sharks
do get the girls, Martin,
you're next in the water.
[Tatiana panting]
[sobbing] He was just finally
getting his life together,
and they killed him.
He killed him. What kind of
psychopath murders kids?
He will murder us too
if we don't do what we're told.
-I'm just scared, Kayle.
-I know, I know. Me too.
Oh my God. [sobs]
But we don't have a choice.
We made a deal.
We have to get that bag.
-[both panting]
-[Kayle] Oh my God.
[Tatiana] TJ. Oh, shit.
We can't go out there.
We're never gonna make it.
[Kayle] What else are
we gonna do? Call the police?
Wait, can we? Don't I have
an SOS thing on my phone?
-Yes, yes.
-My God. Yes, yes, yes! Do it.
[Tatiana breathes shakily]
It's weak,
but I have a signal.
Okay, okay, okay.
How long did it take us
to get here from the shore?
Uh... 30 minutes?
-Maybe...
-Mm-hmm?
If we breathe slow,
we can save air.
-Okay.
-And we can hold them off
long enough for the police
to get here.
-What's your timer say?
-Uh...
I think I have enough air
for another half hour.
I have 45 minutes.
[sighs]
That's cutting it close, T.
Well, I saw an air tank
come down with Danny, right?
If one of us runs out of oxygen,
we should be able to grab that
tank and swap it with ours.
Okay, let's hope
we don't have to.
We can do this. I love you.
-Me too, okay?
-We're gonna be all right.
[Outlaw Ritual's
"I don't Feel at Home" playing]
Scrubbing is not
going to fix that.
[Martin] $400 pants, bro.
If you want to get respect,
first you have to dress to
impress, G-man. You know what?
You should try it.
There is absolutely nothing
that impresses me about you.
Hey, what are you saying?
I got game.
Huh? I got game, baby.
-Game, huh?
-Yeah.
No. Just ego.
[sniffles]
[song ends]
Hello? Everything all right?
[Tatiana] Yeah.
I'm just looking for your bag.
Good, good.
For a moment, I thought
something unfortunate
had happened.
You mean like our two friends
and my brother being murdered?
Your brother? Yeah.
That's unfortunate.
You know, just get my bag.
Your bag is surrounded
by sharks right now.
Drawn in
by my boyfriend's blood.
So that just might
not be possible, all right?
You said the word yourself.
"Deal."
So I expect you to honor it.
Listen, you want your damn bag?
You'll have to wait.
Got it, asshole?
Hey! Come on!
"Asshole"?
Deal's off.
Bring them up.
-They just need more time.
-Now!
[humming]
Oh my God,
they're pulling us up.
[Tatiana] Shit!
You just had to call him
an asshole, didn't you?
You're really gonna school me
on how to talk to a murderer?
I mean, T...
Hold on. I think I got an idea.
Hold on. [panting]
Tatiana, what are you doing?
-Hold on.
-Are you crazy?
Tatiana!
-[rattling]
-[Tatiana breathing shakily]
[air hissing]
[Tatiana grunting]
Come on, come on. Come on!
[grunts then breathing shakily]
[Kayle] Hey! Hey! Shark! Shark!
[Tatiana] Oh my God!
Oh my God! [yells]
Tatiana, are you okay?
It's okay. It just...
It knocked me, okay?
[Kayle] That's what they do.
They bump you,
and then they come back
to bite you.
[Tatiana]
That's one really big fish.
Kayle, the speargun, now.
[Kayle breathing shakily]
[Tatiana] Okay. There's plenty
of fish out there.
It won't bother us.
Just keep eyes on it, yeah?
[groaning]
Oh my God!
[grunting]
Oh, that ain't no shark, man.
That's a fucking submarine
with teeth.
[Logan] It's a great white.
Ain't no guppy.
I've seen him before.
Scarred head.
The locals said
the injury made him mad.
If it's the same one,
he's a killer, I'll tell you.
An old friend?
Came around here
about 20 years ago.
Thought he was gone.
We were wrong.
He's back.
[groans] We can't just be
pinned down by this bolt.
[grunts] It's not going anywhere
unless we take the weight off.
-We have to do something, T.
-[thud]
[yells] Hold on. Hold on, Kayle.
-Kayle.
-Oh my God.
Kayle, hold on. I'm coming.
It's sinking. T, it's sinking!
[Tatiana] Hold on!
[Kayle grunts]
-[yells then whimpers]
-Kayle?
[Kayle] Oh, no! [groans]
Fuck! The speargun.
[groans then whimpers]
[rattling]
[groans]
They're really testing me.
-Martin?
-Yes, boss?
-Suit up.
-Why?
Your turn.
[sighs]
Go, now.
Fuck.
-[Kayle breathes shakily]
-Oh my God, Kayle.
The speargun went off.
Well, it missed the bone.
Thank God.
-Okay, let me see it.
-[yells in pain] No, no!
Okay, okay.
I know it hurts. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm just trying to help you.
But you've gotta
save your air, okay?
-[whimpering] Okay. [yells]
-You have to breathe slow.
I think
I can get the spearhead off.
I think you're supposed
to leave these things in place.
You're risking more damage
with it in place.
I'm trusting you. [grunts]
I just need you to hold still
and hold on to this.
-I'll pull it out on three.
-Okay.
-[whimpers]
-One...
[Kayle yells then whimpering]
It's out, okay?
That's what counts.
Just keep pressure on the wound.
The bleeding should clot fast.
You're lucky it's not worse.
You're gonna be fine.
Yeah? Okay, let's reload it
and do it on you next, okay?
Kayle, just breathe. You've been
using up a lot of your oxygen.
How much time do you have left?
Ten minutes.
Okay, I'm gonna go
find Danny's tank.
Bring it back for you.
Hey, or we could just inflate
our vests and go up now.
You know that guy up there?
The one who killed
TJ, Danny and Kyle?
He's gonna kill us, too.
You get that, right?
We stay down here
as long as we can.
Now I'm getting that tank.
Just keep pressure on your arm.
If you see any more sharks,
use this.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
I'm taking the speargun
and the flare.
[Kayle] Okay...
-Be careful, okay?
-I will.
When you get the bag,
get a good grip on it.
Press that button, okay?
Brings you right up.
-[air hissing]
-Okay. Okay, I got it.
All right, I got it.
Okay. This fucking shit...
[grunts]
There you go. [exhales] Huh?
What did you do that for?
So the sharks
will swim over there, Cap,
because I'm gonna be
over here.
All that did
is attract more sharks.
Yeah. Over there.
I've sailed with fools before,
but you've set a new standard.
And that's saying something.
I'm honored too, Cap.
-Martin.
-Yeah?
[Garrison]
Just stay alive, yeah?
-Yeah.
-Hmm.
Just get the bag.
Okay. Yeah. Let's do this.
Okay.
Yeah.
[muffled] Ooh! That's it.
I got this, G.
I got it.
[Tatiana panting]
Oh! Shit.
Where are you going?
No, no, no. Go back. Shit!
Kayle, keep a lookout.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, never better. You?
Yeah. Okay.
I just need to find the tank.
You got this. Just keep looking.
-[loud thud]
-[screams]
-Hey, Tatiana.
-You okay?
You know that monster white
that's circling us?
[Tatiana] Shit. What's going on?
It's invited a friend over.
An even bigger one.
Just stay in the cage, Kayle,
and keep breathing slow, okay?
You're safe in the cage.
[beeping]
[gasps] Oh...
Danny.
[Martin] You forget about me,
sweet cheeks? [laughs]
-What are you doing?
-Yeah.
-No!
-What the fuck?
-[breathes shakily]
-Stay back!
I just need to inspect
your mask.
I said stay back!
[Martin] I wish it was
different, kid, I really do.
But I'm not dying for you.
-[Tatiana yells]
-[groans in pain]
Bitch! Get this out of me.
You want me
to pull it out for you?
Here, let me help!
[groans] God! You've gone
and fucked up big time.
I'm gonna lose it on you.
Come here. [pants] Come here.
Holy shit! That is big.
Oh, God.
-[Tatiana screams]
-[Martin] What? Jesus!
Hey! Hey! Get the speargun.
Let it go.
-Let it go. Shit!
-Here.
Take that! [grunts]
[Martin groans]
[groans]
[Martin screaming]
[continues screaming]
[dramatic music playing]
[groaning]
[groans]
Okay, Kayle, I've got the tank.
-How much time do you have?
-Four minutes.
-[beeping]
-T, please, hurry. Hurry.
[panting] I'm headed your way.
-Just hold on.
-[intense suspenseful music]
[panting]
Oh! Shit! [groaning]
Come on!
Hey! I'm here.
T! Oh my God, you got it.
Yes. I'm almost out.
Less than 30 seconds.
Okay, I'm gonna swap out
your tank.
I can figure it out.
I'm gonna figure it out.
Just trust me, okay?
Okay, okay.
[device beeping]
[Kayle] Five seconds.
Yeah. Okay.
Just hold your breath.
I'm screwing the valve now.
Come on! Come on! [groans]
[breathes shakily]
[groans]
Almost there. I'm almost there.
-Go! That should be it.
-[air hissing]
Kayle, you good?
[exhales] It's working.
You did it!
-Oh, thank God.
-T, there's so many sharks.
-I know.
-Who was that on our channel?
The creepy smoker. Yeah.
Remember him?
I guess they sent him down
for the bag.
He tried to kill me,
so I shot him.
-[beeping]
-Is that you or me?
-Uh... Me?
-[beeping continues]
Ten minutes? T, what the hell?
What are you gonna do?
Shit. Okay, okay.
Just let me think.
-I have an idea.
-Tell me.
-What is it?
-Just hold on.
Hey, asshole.
Remember me?
[sighs]
How could I forget you, Tatiana?
So your boy tried to shoot me.
He won't be shooting anyone
ever again.
Well, that's too bad.
You still want your bag?
More than you can imagine,
Tatiana.
Here's how I see it. I don't
know you. You don't know me.
The only guy we can identify
is about to be shark shit.
I'm gonna get that bag for you.
I'm gonna send it up. You're
gonna take off on your boat,
and once you're gone,
we'll get back on ours
and get on with our lives.
Deal?
You have yourself a deal.
[taps twice]
[mutters] Okay.
I'm gonna go find that guy
and grab his tank.
[beeping]
That should buy us
some time. Shit.
I have to go. I'll see you soon.
Good luck.
[Tatiana sighs]
[breathing shakily]
Where are you?
[eerie music playing]
[gasps] There you are.
Okay. Hey, I found him.
Well, what's left of him.
[sighs]
[Kayle] Great.
Can you put his tank on now?
[sighs] Well, I'm gonna try.
Okay.
Let's get this off of you.
Come on.
Oh, fuck!
[grunts]
Come on. Oh, God. [sighs]
Come on. [groans]
[grunts] Fuck!
[panting]
Okay, okay.
Oh... Shit! Shit! No!
[groans] Shit! Shit!
[breathing shakily] No!
No! No!
[whimpering]
Oh, shit!
-[beeping]
-[panting]
Damn it!
You can do this.
[Kayle] Pretty good. Oh my God.
My God, my God. Okay.
-Attagirl.
-[Tatiana] Okay. Come on.
-Okay. I have his tank.
-Pretty good. Oh my God.
My God, my God. Okay.
-Attagirl.
-[groans] Okay.
[whimpering]
[groans]
[panting] Oh...
Switching masks.
Okay. You can do this.
You can do this.
[inhales then groans]
[gasping]
-[air hissing]
-[breathing slowly]
Oh my God.
Kayle, can you hear me?
-I just switched my tank.
-Oh, thank you, God!
-[faint humming in distance]
-[Tatiana] Wait a minute.
-Do you hear that?
-It's another boat.
Yes!
Should we swim
to the surface now?
No. Wait. Just wait.
We'll go together.
Just give me a minute.
Because I have two really
big sharks circling me.
[Delgado in Spanish]
[in English] We do?
[in Spanish]
[in English]
Garrison, lose the kid's body.
Delgado, get the bags on my boat
and get rid of Drago's body.
Already taken care of, boss.
You see?
Did you see that?
Delgado handled it.
You want to be respected?
Earn it!
Sure.
-[coughs]
-[Garrison] Shit!
-What is it now?
-He's still alive.
All right, just put him below
and make sure he stays quiet.
[groans]
[sighs]
Capitán, put on some music.
We are about
to have ourselves a party.
And if you so much as hint
to those cops about the girls,
I won't only kill you.
I will kill them too.
And your son will die screaming.
Aye, aye.
I'm very picky with the music,
so... don't mess it up.
[siren blaring]
[Outlaw Ritual's
"Trouble in My Time" playing]
♪ I don't know
What's good for me ♪
♪ When all I've ever learned
Is how to lie ♪
♪ Well, the hidden hands
Of wisdom ♪
♪ Holds all that
It can keep... ♪
[in Spanish]
[in English] Uh... English.
Sorry, I don't speak español.
Everyone on the deck! Now!
What...? What seems to be
the problem, officer?
Are these all the passengers?
Yeah. That's it.
Do you have
a Tatiana Scott on board?
No, no. Just us hombres.
Do you recognize her?
Yeah, I believe she was
on our last tour.
-Why?
-We received an SOS signal
from her phone.
The ping was in this location.
Uh...
-Is she American?
-That's right. Yeah.
I recall her losing her phone
while she was in the cage.
Mind if we look around?
No, no. Go ahead. Yeah.
[in Spanish]
[Kayle]
You think that's the police?
It has to be.
Otherwise, why would they stop?
Can somebody hear us? Hello?
Hey! Hi! We're down here.
Where's your shark cage?
Oh, I'm in the process
of getting a new one.
You know, safety protocols
and whatnot.
Yours wasn't safe?
No, no, just routine
maintenance, you know?
Why aren't they answering us?
We're down here!
Kayle, you have to calm down.
I think I'm being
extremely calm,
considering
the circumstances, T.
Hey, remember what I told you:
breathe slow and keep pressure
on that arm.
Okay, but we have to head up.
-We should just go for it.
-Yeah.
You gotta give me
another minute.
I really need these sharks
to leave first, please.
-T, I'm gonna try.
-No, not with your arm.
-I can make it.
-Let's just wait.
Kyle's body is still up there.
Maybe they'll find him, and then
they'll have to look for us.
[officer 1 in Spanish]
[in English] Are you married?
Yes.
-Do you have kids?
-Yes, I have kids.
There's nothing like family.
It's for them.
[officer 2] I checked
Tatiana's social media.
She posted a picture
this morning,
getting ready
to go shark diving.
Well, like I said, you know,
she was on my last tour,
lost her phone
and I dropped them off.
But I thought you said
you were getting a new cage.
Yeah, I got rid of the old one
this morning.
Everything is good below.
Let's let these men
finish their party.
But I have a few more questions.
[in Spanish]
[Kayle] This is taking too long.
I'm gonna try. I'm sorry, T.
I can't miss my only chance.
-Kayle!
-It's fine.
-I'm going up.
-Kayle, stay where you are.
Hello?
Shit!
Damn it!
Kayle, get back in the cage!
I can't see the sharks.
Seriously, they could be
headed toward you.
Answer me, Kayle! Damn it!
[creaking]
Please, please,
just stay in the cage.
Just... God! Kayle,
we have to go up together.
Can you answer me, please?
Can you hear me?
The BCD isn't working.
It isn't taking me up.
-Come on.
-The pressure is too low.
Just stay where you are.
Oh my God, Kayle.
Hold on.
[ominous music playing]
[Kayle screams]
-Oh! Shit!
-Oh my God! [yells]
-[whimpering]
-Kayle, what just happened?
[breathes shakily] My leg.
Kayle, it's okay, it's okay.
Kayle, what is going on?
[Kayle whimpers]
Listen, I need you to tell me
what is happening.
-What's wrong? Kayle!
-[whimpering]
[sobbing]
Kayle.
I'm in the cage!
-Okay, that's good.
-Okay.
Just... Just stay calm.
Let me think. Let me think.
You have a tourniquet
on your vest?
-There's a lot of blood.
-I know.
Just use that to stop
the bleeding, okay?
It's gonna be okay.
Just put it above the wound.
And watch your breathing, okay?
You're using up all your oxygen.
[whimpers]
I'm losing a lot of blood.
I know, but you've gotta
pull it tight. Come on.
[screams]
[Burns] Hey.
Please understand that
I'm gonna check their hotel.
If they aren't there, I will
continue this investigation.
And if I can't locate Tatiana
Scott or any of her friends,
expect a new visit from me.
-All right.
-Morales!
Well, I hope you find them.
-[Tatiana] Are they leaving?
-[Kayle] No, they can't leave.
They can't leave.
No, no, no, no!
They can't leave us.
They're not gonna leave us.
I got an idea. [panting]
I'm sending
the creepy smoker up.
[groans]
Kayle, I'm heading back to you.
Just hold on.
[in Spanish]
[Kayle whimpering]
-Kayle!
-[gasps]
Kayle! I'm here, I'm here.
It's gonna be okay.
-Oh my God!
-[continues whimpering]
Oh my God.
There's so much blood.
-Oh my God.
-[breathes shakily]
We need to get you
to the surface.
I'm not sure I can swim.
I'm so sorry, Kayle,
but the police are leaving.
We need to get you up.
We don't have much time.
We need to get moving.
[police siren blaring]
Well?
Oh, shit.
Hey, I've got you.
Okay? I've got you.
-[whimpering]
-Just keep going.
-[groaning]
-We're almost there.
[in Spanish]
[groaning]
Martin. Martin. Martin.
[both groaning]
[Kayle whimpering]
Help!
[in Spanish]
-[gasps for air]
-Help! She's hurt! Help!
-Help!
-Morales!
-[Kayle whimpers]
-Hey!
Well, we're fucked.
-Come on!
-Help! She's hurt! Help us!
[officer 1 in Spanish]
Hey, come here!
-What are you smiling at?
-[indistinct yelling]
Help! Help us! Here!
[in Spanish]
[indistinct yelling]
[yelling indistinctly]
[Tatiana] Here!
[in Spanish] Come on!
-[Kayle] Help!
-Delgado! Now!
[rapid gunshots]
-Nice.
-Morales!
[choking]
Keep going, keep going.
[gunshots]
Wow!
[both screaming, muttering]
-Holy shit! Holy shit!
-[Burns laughing]
That was amazing, Delgado!
Burns, what the hell
are you doing?
That was fantastic, isn't it?
You can't blow up
a bloody police boat.
I can blow up whatever I want.
Keep running your mouth
and your boat is next.
[whimpers]
You're okay. Hold me.
Hold on. You're okay.
It's okay, Kayle, it's okay.
Come on, come on.
Any sign of Martin?
What was left of him
was on that boat.
I am not leaving without my bag.
-[Kayle screams]
-Hold me, hold me.
[whimpering]
-[Kayle whimpering]
-Hold on. [grunts]
[whimpering]
Finally. Yeah! We meet properly.
Don't just stand there.
Help her!
You heard the lady.
Help her, come on.
[Kayle crying]
You have to be careful.
[Kayle yelling]
-[Tatiana] Careful!
-[breathing shakily]
-Kayle, it's okay, it's okay.
-[groaning]
-[screams]
-[Tatiana] Careful!
I know it hurts,
just stay awake.
Please, Kayle! Kayle!
Can somebody find
a first aid kit?
Help me, please!
Or she's gonna die.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Oh my God. Oh my God.
-My God!
-[Kayle screams]
[Logan] I need you
to release this tourniquet
every 15 minutes, all right?
And keep that leg elevated.
-It's okay, Kayle.
-Keep it warm.
We got her, we got her.
-Okay, okay.
-There you go.
-Hey, hey.
-She's lost a lot of blood.
We need to get her
to a hospital.
Yeah, yeah.
You heard that, Tatiana?
If you want your friend
to leave,
you better deliver
on your end of our deal.
You know, I mean, my bag
and this will all be over, eh?
-I won't.
-Hey. What?
-I can't.
-You can! I know you can!
Damn it, Burns,
I told you I'd go!
I know this shark!
It's a man-eater!
The girl was lucky once,
all right? Let me go.
-I'll get your goods.
-[Burns] No, you won't!
This is between her and me.
Okay? So now sit down
or I will kill you,
burn your boat,
murder your son
and never think about you again!
So, listen, Tatiana. Yeah.
I have been
extremely patient with you,
and I don't like
to make things personal.
But you have left me
no other choice.
And I understand
you two know each other.
-T! T!
-Kyle! Kyle!
Please, let me up.
Wait! Let me up!
No, no. Stay there. No, no, no.
Until I get my bag, okay?
Just stay there.
[Kyle breathes shakily]
I'm fine. I'm fine.
What is that?
Oh.
Wow! Look at this. [chuckles]
Cards have been the undoing
of many a man.
But they spared you.
You are a lucky young man.
But you hurt your head, you see?
-[Kyle groaning]
-That's enough!
[Kyle continues groaning]
That's enough, that's enough.
Stop! Stop, stop! [cries]
No, this is just a warm-up,
you know?
A blowtorch, some rock salt...
By the time I am done,
your brother will thank me
for killing him!
Okay, okay. I'll go. I'll go.
Just stop.
[stammers]
It's funny. You know how...
a little well-placed brutality
can solve what talk never could.
[Logan] Look.
This mesh, it'll protect you
against the curious bite,
but not an attack, all right?
Should or will?
I've no idea. Never had
the guts to check it myself.
I'll be sure to put it
on my Yelp review.
You have a fresh tank
and a new BCD.
With the weight of the bag,
it'll take a while for you
to get back into the surface.
Anything comes near you,
go for the eyes. Got it?
Stay confident.
Turn to face the shark
and don't break eye contact.
Sharks rely on the element
of surprise.
Facing them shows awareness.
They don't like it.
You got this.
I'll come back for you guys.
I'll take care of them.
Don't worry.
[air hissing]
Shark mesh, huh?
It won't help.
God.
Where is it?
Come on.
Okay.
[ominous music playing]
[breathes shakily]
Fuck.
Not today, you ugly bastard.
[humming]
You okay, kid?
-Better.
-Good.
You keep talking to her
and keep her warm, all right?
We're gonna be fine
if we do what we're told.
You want something?
[softly]
Now, you take the knife.
[stammering] I can't.
Shit. Okay, okay. Fine.
[Logan]
You'll know when to use it.
Okay. Okay.
[footsteps departing]
[sobbing] I'm so sorry, TJ.
I'm just... so sorry.
[sobbing]
[continues sobbing]
[wailing]
[continues wailing]
Goodbye.
[breathes shakily]
[exhales]
Okay.
I've got the bag. I'm headed up.
Sorry for the delay.
I got caught up.
Good girl.
We will worry about you.
Well, this day's really
starting to turn around,
isn't it, Capitán?
No...
No. [breathes shakily]
[yelling]
Stay away! [groans]
Okay.
Okay. You want to mess with me?
Okay. [grunts]
Look at me.
-[roars]
-[screams]
[grunting]
[yelling]
[panting]
[breathing shakily]
[sighs]
[gasps]
You've gotta be kidding me.
[panting]
Shit! Shit! Shit!
[roars]
There.
I can do this. [panting]
I can do this.
I'm gonna make this
right for you.
[groaning]
-[heroic music playing]
-[breathes relieved]
I got the bag!
There she is.
If you want this,
you're gonna have to help me.
Tatiana!
Amazing, Tatiana! Bring her up.
Garrison!
Come on, man, move your ass!
[Tatiana groans] Take it.
Take it. Just take it. [groans]
The bag. The bag.
Just give me the goddamn bag.
Yeah.
Kyle! Is she okay?
Look at that. Wow, we did it.
For a moment I thought that this
was going to be impossible,
but here we are.
[exhales deeply]
-[sighs]
-[Tatiana] So...
You're gonna let us go, right?
Well, you completed
your end of the deal,
so I'll do as I said.
Logan, I'll be seeing you.
Garrison, I'll call you
when the new shipment is in.
And... [in Spanish]
[sucks teeth] Oh! Oh!
One more thing.
-I am lying.
-[suspenseful music playing]
Delgado.
-[grunts]
-[Delgado groans]
Oh!
[roars]
[breathes shakily]
[Burns groans]
No.
You know, I mean...
Boy, you've got balls,
and I respect that.
Fuck you!
Yeah, well, it doesn't change
what comes next.
Garrison, the gun.
Garrison!
-Sorry, boss.
-What?
I'm not gonna do that for you.
-Huh?
-You always say
it's about business,
it's not personal, right?
Well, this seems to be
fucking personal to me.
So the gun stays with me.
It's nice you've been listening
to me.
But if you have been listening
to me,
you probably heard me saying,
"No loose ends!"
[Burns muttering]
You know? [sighs]
It's okay. Because...
I made my first killing
with a knife.
[grunts]
You stole my life.
Your good-for-nothing
son's habit stole your life.
I gave you an option,
so I didn't have to take his.
[gunshots]
[Burns groans]
I think it's time
you take your bag...
-[Burns] Hey, hey.
-...and get off this boat.
-Hey...
-Listen to me,
you boomer motherfucker!
You murdered my friends,
injured my family
and ruined my vacation.
I should shoot you
where you stand right now.
And the only reason
you're still breathing
is because I'm choosing
to show restraint.
You're done here.
Off this boat. Now!
Before I change my fucking mind.
You know?
I think I'm on my way out
after all.
But, trust me, this is most
definitely not the end.
I'll be seeing you.
Especially you, Tatiana.
[panting]
[soft music playing]
[engine starts]
Hey, are you okay?
Are you okay?
No. Are you?
You don't get to play games
with your life anymore, okay?
Because,
whether you like it or not,
I'm in this with you, too.
I don't plan on it. [sniffles]
[Kyle sighs]
Is he gonna come after us?
Absolutely.
Why'd you help us?
Anyone that went through
what you went through
deserves to walk away.
He should have kept
his end of the bargain.
I thought
he was a man of principle.
Turns out
he was just batshit crazy.
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
[flare whistles]
-Shit!
-[flare continues whistling]
[gasps]
For emergencies.
And that was certainly
an emergency.
That's what you were doing
when you checked the fuel.
What if I'd gone on the boat?
I wouldn't have done that,
would I?
Get us a drink.
Let's get you three
to the hospital.
-Thank you, Captain.
-[Kayle and Logan groan]
-[Kayle groans]
-Okay. Hey.
Keep it elevated, all right?
[softly] All right.
[exhales]
Did I ever tell you
about the Irish
-who fought at the Alamo?
-I don't think so.
Well, they were so badly treated
by their own gang,
they switched sides
and joined the Mexican army.
[sighs] Oh my God.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[melancholic music playing]
[music fades out]
[downtempo music playing]
[tense music playing]
[music ends]